自天地初开之时
[Man Narrating] Since time began...
世界就被一场在
a war has been waged in the shadows...
正义和邪恶之间的战争所笼罩着
between the armies ofGood and Evil.
这场战争可能惊天地泣鬼魂
It may be fought on a grand scale...
也可能只是在小孩之间的心魔之战
or within the heart ofa single individual-or even a child.
邪恶力量无处不在
The Evil has taken many forms...
它被黑暗所支配着
and used the darkest ofarts.
在现代，他们被称作
In our time, they call themselves simply...
幻影杀手
the Hand.
正义总是站在善良的一方
The Good follow the way ofki magure.
仁慈之主不但可以看到未来
Its masters can see the future...
甚至能够起死回生
and perhaps even bring back the dead.
这是个武魂的传奇故事
Legend tells of a unique warrior...
她是一颗失落的灵魂
a lost soul.
她是个女战士
This warrior is a woman...
她是个孤儿
a motherless daughter.
上天安排她去平息这场 正义与邪恶之战
And it is her destiny to tip the balance between Good and Evil.
有个小孩是力量之源 双方都需要她的协助
She is a treasure, and both sides seek her out...
她将成为战争中的终极武器
as a final weapon in an ancient war.
片名：艾丽卡 又名：幻影杀手
- 你那有什么动静吗？ - 一切正常
- [ Man ] Perimeter, what's your status? - [ Man #2 ] Delta team, clear.
- 一切正常 - 一切正常
- [ Man #3 ] Alpha, clear. - [ Man #4 ] Bravo, secure.
没有用的
It doesn't matter.
你阻止不了她的
You can't stop her.
- 没人能阻止她 - 就凭她？
- Nobody can stop her. - Her?
恐怕这次你无法完成任务
I was afraid if I told you, you wouldn't take the job.
我本来是不想请你出山的
I never should've hired you.
冲你来的那个人到底是谁？
Who doyou think's coming foryou?
你也许听说过她，她叫…
You may have heard ofher. Her name...
艾丽卡
is Elektra.
- 你觉得这个很好笑吗？ - 她是城里一段传奇
- You find that funny? - She's an urban legend, sir.
几年前就死了
That woman died years ago.
真的？ 那应该派人把她的尸体带回来
Really? Well, then somebody must have brought her back from the dead.
鲍尔，知道吗？ 我们的所作所为
You know, Bauer, whenyou've done the things I've done...
给我们树立了好多敌人
you make a lot of enemies.
我花巨款买来的密报说
My private security detail- the best money could buy.
这个死掉的女人 在半个小时内杀了14个人
This nonexistent woman killed 1 4 of them in half an hour.
我都不敢离开这里
I barelygot away.
奇怪的是，在蒙特卡洛时 她居然放过我
Spent the next two days in Monte Carlo wondering why she let me go.
而现在却又向我杀来
Then she came for me.
原本是幻影杀手负责我的安全 而她曾经是他们的一分子
I was underthe protection ofthe Hand itself, who sent theirbest.
现在组织为了杀她 已经不管我得死活
Although theyseemed more interested in killing Elektra than in protecting me.
把这些保镖碾个粉碎
She cut 'em down I i ke wheat.
她只需要10分钟，最多15分钟
T ook maybe 1 0, 1 5 m i nutes max.
我不能再袖手旁观
Didn't really think why I kept gettin' away.
这是我来的目的
So here I am.
我现在了解她了
And now I understand her.
她想让我尝尝这种滋味
She wanted me to feel this...
像是走头无路
what it's like to have nowhere to go...
无人求援
nowhere to turn.
你现在感觉怎么样？
How's yourperimeter doing now?
德尔塔，你那里情况怎么样？
Delta, what's your status?
没有反应 臭婊子
There's no signal. Son of a bitch.
- 你知道吗，这种刺客喜欢 - 阿尔法，布莱欧，请回答
- You know, the better the assassin- -Alpha, Bravo, report!
在你知道她的行踪之前 她会先慢慢逼近，然后干掉你
the closer they can get to you before you know they're there.
阿尔法，布莱欧，请回答
Alpha! Bravo! Report!
该死
- [ Static ] - Ah, Christ.
他们说在艾丽卡杀你之前 会在你耳边说悄悄话
They say Elektra whispers in your ear before she kills you.
- 阿尔法，布莱欧，请回答 - 老板现在太晚了，鲍尔
- Alpha! Bravo! Report! - [ Woman ] It's too late foryour boss, Bauer.
- 但你还是有机会的 - 哦，该死
- But you still have a chance. -Jesus Christ!
你无法与鬼魂战斗
[Woman ] You can't fight a ghost, Bauer.
该到我们了
- Here we are at last. - [ Exhales ]
跟传说的一模一样
Guess it's all true.
红色的衣服 还有那把刀
The red outfit and the knives and-
现在你想怎么样？
So, what happens now?
毫不犹豫地杀了我？
You just kill me, straight out? Just cold?
不要怕 死亡并不是一件很可怕的事
Don't worry. Death's not that bad.
是吗？你怎么知道？
Yeah? How do you know?
我已经死过一次
[ Whispering ] I died once.
是什么感觉？ 有没有...
What's it like? Is there...
白光和上帝？
you know, a white light and God?
我想 我就要知道了
What- I guess I'll find out.
我也明白幻影杀手的力量
So am I to understand that with all the power ofthe Hand...
我们的头号杀手 还在躲避着我们？
that the Treasure continues to elude us?
对，我们本应该更早点采取行动
Yes. Perhaps ifwe had pursued it sooner...
向她发动更大的攻势
and more aggressively-
你胆敢怪罪帮主罗侍郎？
You dare to blame Master Roshi?
也许克阮你太掉以轻心了
Seems our methods are too mild for Kirigi.
根本没有
Not at all, sensei.
如果我们不能得到这个力量之源
But ifwe cannot have the weapon ourselves...
也不能让她落入敌人的手里
allow me to make sure it does not fall into the hands ofthose who may use it against us.
帮主，请让我插几句
Master, allow me.
这个事情一定要尽快地 悄悄地解决
Things like this must be handled smoothly, quietly.
那就悄悄地去办吧，马之密 但一定要快
Then work smoothly, Meizumi, but quickly.
克阮
Kirigi?
什么事？爸爸
Yes, Father.
耐心点
Patience.
你怎么门都不锁 一点安全意识都没有
[Man ] You think that's safe, leaving the door unlocked like that?
艾丽卡，一颗子弹就能结束你
Geez, Elektra, you're gonna end up with a bullet in your head.
我给你带了点东西
I brought you a little something.
等下，不要放在那里 我刚刚擦好
No, stop, McCabe. Don't put it down. I al ready cleaned there.
- 为什么你整天的清洗这里？ - 擦除我的DNA
- Why do you always do this? - Get rid of my D.N.A.
啊，DNA，说得没错
Ah, D.N.A., of course. Right.
我真傻，这个是我刚拿到的 你一定想看看
Silly of me. Listen, I just picked this up. I knowyou like to look.
- 全部在里面了？ - 连我的一成也没到
- It's all there? - Less my 1 0%.
- 到巴巴多斯岛拿一半 - 还有一半要到马恩岛拿
- Halfto Barbados? - And halfto the bank on the Isle of Man.
其实你可以赚更多 我知道一个人，我帮你联系他
You can do better in mutual funds. I know a guy. I could putyou in touch-
- 不用了，谢谢 - 不要了？但是...
- No, thanks. - Or not. But-
听我说，其实我不想干涉你的事情
Look, I don't want to tell you how to doyour thing...
但是这一次 有很多人抢这个生意
but quite a body count on this one, E.
难道我们只能为丹马克卖命
We were only getting paid for DeMarco.
非得这样吗？
Was it necessary?
是不得不
Had to be done.
是吗？
Did it?
艾丽卡
Elektra.
是吗？
Did it?
好吧
Okay.
我们要紧尊师父的教诲
Anyway, it spreads the legend.
否则，我会死的
Besides, theywere gonna kill me.
这个说的没错
Of course they were. Absolutely.
但是听你的特工小组说
And, speaking ofwhich, as your agent...
这是一件及其重要的任务
I am obligated to tell you we just got an absolutely fantastic new offer...
- 也是你最后的任务 - 我们不要谈这个了，我需要休息一下
- but that last job- - Let's skip this one. I need a breather.
- 那好吧，我只是说这次报酬很高 - 我已经很累了
- Great idea. I'm just sayin' it's a lot of coin. - I'm tired.
你真的累了？ 那你还真需要好好睡一觉
You're tired? Well, then you better getyourselfsome sleep...
否则你很快会垮掉的
'causeyou are gonna crash, baby, you know that.
你好像从来都没有休息过的样子
I mean, you even get laid?
这次任务报酬真的很多
It's a lot of money, this new offer.
- 曼柯 - 好，好吧
- McCabe. - All right, fine. You know what?
那你慢慢休息一下 你想行动的时候打电话给我
Look, you want to take time off, take time off. Call me when you wanna work.
多少钱？说吧
How much? And just tell me.
两百万
Two.
他们也可能雇其他杀手
Ah, they'll give it to somebody else.
他们不会付给别人这么多的
Theywouldn't pay that to somebody else.
你说得对
You got that right.
他们很想你去处理这件事
They asked specifically foryou.
地点在那里面 找到目标以后通知你
Location's in there. I'll call you when I get the target.
好好睡会吧
Get some sleep.
再试一次
- Again! - [ Man ] Clear!
你知道你的方向吗，艾丽卡
[Man's Voice ] Doyou knowthe way, Elektra?
意念，可以让你控制时间
[Man's Voice Continuing] Kimagure, the abilityto control time...
看到未来
the future...
甚至可以起死回生
even life and death.
我知道我是这里最好的学生
[ Elektra ] I know I'm the best student here.
不是最好的 但是最有力量的
Not the best. The most powerful.
你明白暴力和痛苦
You understand violence and pain.
但你还没有领悟到突破的出路
But you do not know the way.
- 那请你教我吧 - 这个我办不到
- Teach me then. - That's my point.
这个不是教出来的
I can't teach you.
我要你离开这里
I want you to go.
这个算是测验吗？师傅
Is this a test, sensei?
不是测验
No, not a test.
走吧
Just go.
我没有地方去
I don't have anywhere to go.
委托人说要你 早几天到行动地点
[McCabe ] The clientsays he needsyou there a couple days early...
这也是你的报酬中的部分行动
says that's part ofthe deal.
- 为什么 - 不知道
- [ Elektra ] Why? - No idea.
- 他只是想你在那里等他消息 - 看来我不得不去了
- He just wants you to wait. - I just want to get this over with.
我知道，其实那里的风景不错
Hey, me too. Listen, why don't you tell me about the view?
听说那里风景秀丽 你知道，如果你到...
I hear it's gorgeous out there. You know, you got the-
继续艾丽卡，坚持住
- [Man ] Come on, Elektra. Keep pedaling. - [ Gasps ]
再坚持5分钟
Five more minutes.
不要用手 别想偷懒，只能用脚
Don't use your hands. Don't be lazy. Only use your feet.
坚持住 踩水，踩水...
Let's go! Let's push, push, push, push!
尼姑拉斯，亲爱的，该休息了 她只是个孩子
Nikolas. Honey, please. She'sjust a kid.
继续，艾丽卡
[Nikolas ] Keep going, Elektra.
继续踩
Keep going.
天哪，你疯了 你差点杀了我
Jesus! What's the matter with you? You could have killed me!
你在这里干吗？
What are you doing here?
没什么 我只是在这里随便走走
Nothing. I'm friends with the Wheelwrights.
真实糟糕 你把我的大衣弄坏了
[ Sighs ] Damn it. You cut my friggin' jacket.
- 你怎么进去的？ - 门根本就没有锁
- How did you get in? - The front doorwas unlocked.
- 不可能 - 它是没有锁
- No, it wasn't. - Yeah, it was.
住在这里的人都让我随便出入 不信你去问
[ Sighs ] Look, the people who live here let me come in all the time. Ask anybody.
好像是坏了
Hmm. It's broken.
- 你是？我的名字是艾比 - 你偷了什么东西
- So, who areyou anyways? My name's Abby. - What'd you steal?
什么都没有 你把我当成什么？
[ Sighs ] Nothing. What doyou think I am?
求你不要叫警察
Please don't call the cops.
我老爸会打死我的
My dad will kill me.
在某些地方的只是要 剁掉小偷的手
In some parts ofthe world, theyjust cutyour hands off.
你怎么弄得？
How did you do that?
给我离开这里
Get out ofhere.
不要担心，艾丽卡
[Man, Distorted] Don't worry, Elektra.
我会好好照顾她的
I'll take good care ofher.
妈妈?
Mom?
哦，妈的
Oh, shit.
我坐不住了，曼柯 快点告诉我目标
[Elektra ] You know I can't sit still, McCabe. Call me with the name.
委托人想让你早点到那里 在那儿等几天
[ McCabe ] Client says he needs you there a couple days early. Wants you to wait.
-　哪儿也不要去 - 死亡并不是那么可怕
- [ DeMarco's Voice ] To have nowhere to go- - Death 's not that bad.
- 无人求援 - 他只是想让你等着
- nowhere to turn. - He wants you to wait.
- 难道就这样杀了我？ - 他想你在那里等着
- Youjust kill me, straight out? - He wants you to wait.
你在找我吗？
[ Elektra ] Are you looking for me?
你好
H i.
你是新来的房客吗？
Are you the new, uh, tenant?
房产经纪人埃迪说 这个月有位年轻的小姐搬来
Eddie Ferris, the Realtor- he said, uh, a young woman had taken it for the month.
关你什么事？
What do you want?
对不起，我也许不该说这个
Sorry. This is kind of awkward, but, uh...
你有没有看到一个13岁 金发的女孩
haveyou seen a girl- 1 3-year-old, uh, blondish hair to about here?
她是我女儿，艾比
My daughter, Abby.
- 我们昨天吵了一架 - 我下午看到她的
- We hada fightyesterday- - I saw her late afternoon.
- 哦，是吗？ - 我闯到了我家里
- Oh, you did? - She broke into my house.
真是气人
Shit. Really?
她总是到处乱跑
Uh, she knows the Wheelwrights, who, uh-
那她拿你什么东西没？
She, uh, didn't take anything, did she?
- 没有 - 那就好
- No. - Good.
如果她打坏你什么东西，我会赔给你 我叫马克・米勒
Look, if she broke something, I'm- I'm happy to pay for it. I'm Mark Miller.
住在那个木屋里，隔你两间房
We're in the little cabin two houses down.
那好吧，谢谢
Okay, thanks.
我是曼柯 只要留下你的名字
[McCabe ] Hi,you've reached McCabe. But please leavejustyour name.
- 请不要留言 - 曼柯
- Do not leave a message. - [ Sighs ] McCabe...
我再坐在这里，就要发疯了
I 'm sick of sitting here.
如果你在弄不到对方的名字 我要离开这里了
We don't get a name soon, I'm walking.
嗨
Hey.
你站在那里多久了？
How long have you been standing there?
大概一分钟
Like, a minute.
你都跟我爸说了些什么？
What did you tell my dad?
你告诉他，我闯到你家去了吗？
Did you tell him I broke intoyour house?
- 说了，因为你的确去了 - 你干吗非告诉他
- Yeah, becauseyou did break in. - Well, you didn't have to tell him.
我还以为你不会计较呢
I thoughtyou were cool.
- 可惜我不是 - 没错，一点都不会骗人
- I'm not. - Yeah, no kidding.
我爸让我来邀请你去 跟我们共进圣诞晚餐
Now he's on my case. He made me come askyou to have Christmas dinnerwith us.
- 什么？
- Have what? - Christmas?
圣诞晚餐，12月25号
Dinner? December25?
你知道今天是圣诞节吗？
Did you know today's Christmas?
谢谢你，但是我不能去 我有事情要做
Thankyou. I can't. I have something to do.
什么事，所有的店都关门了
What? Everything's closed.
你现在在一个孤岛上
You're on an island.
求你了，来吧
Come on. Please?
每天晚上都是我们两个
It's just the two of us every night...
我都厌倦这种生活了
and I'm bored out of my skull.
你在干嘛？
What areyou doing?
没干吗，为什么？
Nothing. Why?
- 你在数什么？ - 没有啊
- Wereyou counting? - No.
你会来的是吧，求你了
So, will you come? Please?
如果你不来，我还会偷到你家去
Because ifyou don't, I'll just keep breaking intoyour house. Hmm?
那我要去换下衣服
Hmm. I have to change my clothes.
太好了
Great!
我叫艾比
I'm Abby.
艾丽卡
Elektra.
艾丽卡，不错
Elektra. Cool.
跟你讲了不要出去
I told you not to leave the house.
- 你根本就不知道我出去了 - 艾比
- You didn't even know I was gone. - Abby.
先暂停爸爸 我们有个客人
Chill, Dad. We have a guest.
对不起 她说是你要她去邀请我的
I'm sorry. She told me that you'd invited me.
我本不想来
I don't want to-
- 我只是
- I'll just- - Hmm. Uh-uh.
没关系的，一起吃饭吧
- [Footsteps Departing] - No. Please, stay.
我很高兴你能来
I'm- I'm gladyou're here.
你要喝点啤酒还是红酒？
Uh, can I get you a beer? Wine?
水
Water.
她叫艾丽卡，爸爸
Her name's Elektra, Dad.
艾丽卡
- ** [ Continues ] - Elektra.
奇怪的名字 你父母一定很幽默吧
Like the tragedy. Your parents must have had a sense of humor.
一点都不
Not really.
爸爸，当她看我这个美男子 像是超越了她所有的朋友
[Abby] So when she sees all the cute guys who like me- just as friends, Dad-
她决定把我画在泰姬陵的墙上 作为他们的代表
she accidentally spills posterpaint all over my model ofthe Taj Mahal.
后来我在她的鼻子上涂了点胶水
So I put gl ue on her shoes.
结果她停止了计划画我的工程 后来由于打架我被赶出了那里
I got suspended for that, and then I got expelled for fighting.
这就是我在...
But that was way back in the day in- in, um...
巴尔的摩的童年生活
Baltimore.
我很好奇你为什么租了 惠尔莱特的房子
So, I was a little surprised to seeyou take the Wheelwright place.
因为很少有人 会在这个时候租他的房子的
Not manyrenters this time ofyear.
我是为工作，在这里住一个月
It's just for the month, forwork.
你是干什么的？
What do you do anyway?
专门做些解雇人
Oh, layoffs, payroll reduction.
缩减工人薪水之类的事情
- That sort ofthing. - Hmm.
- 听上去很无聊的样子 - 艾比
- Sounds boring. - Abby.
没错，是很无聊 我很喜欢你的手镯
No, it is boring. I like your bracelet, by the way.
你知道它代表什么吗？
Do you know what those are? Here.
这是源于印尼水晶珠 它代表武士道精神
They're warrior beads. They're from Indonesia.
在古代，只有村庄 最好的武士才配戴它
Centuries ago, you had to be the best fighter in yourvillage to earn them.
我从网上买的
I bought 'em off eBay.
这岛上有学校吗？
Is there a school here on the island?
我们打算先进行一段家庭式的教育
Uh, we're tryinghomeschooling fora while.
我读过大学的书 自己也可以学代数
I read at college level. And I'm doing algebra one on my own.
她是个不错的学生
She's a goodstudent.
但是他的行为却总是让我失望
It's the, uh, behavioral stuff that's been a problem.
我有权力干自己喜欢的事 我没有必要非听那些唠叨
I have authority issues, and I don't take bullshit well.
- 不要这样对你爸说 - 嗨，艾比
- Don't speak in that- - Hey, Abby!
没关系
It's okay.
这么快她已经是个大人了
Suddenly I got a teenager on my hands.
- 其实她很努力 - 你可以直接跟她说
- She's hard on herself. - You can tell, huh?
- 很多人认为她很懒 - 不，我不认为
- Most people think she's a slacker. - No, I shouldn't.
圣诞快乐
Merry Christmas?
她妈妈呢？
Where's her mother?
她很多年前就死了
She died... a couple ofyears ago.
在巴尔的摩？
Back in Baltimore?
对，酒后驾车
Yeah. Drunk driver.
我很小的时候妈妈就死了
My mother died when I was young.
我应该回去了
I should go.
- 我还有工作要做 - 不是吧，天还早呢
- I have work. - Come on, it's early.
多谢晚餐
Thanks for dinner.
妈妈
Mom.
- 什么事？
- [ Beeps ] - What?
看你的邮包
[ McCabe ] Good morning. You just got a delivery.
- 这次是两个人 - 所以赚双份钱
- It's a double. - Which makes double the money.
这正是赚这么多钱的原因
Yeah, that's why the big bucks.
- 怎么了？ - 没事
- What's the matter? - Nothing.
好吧，没问题最好
Good. Then there'll be no problems.
解决了我会打电话给你
I'll call you when it's done.
你的数学怎么样了？
How's math going?
你觉得呢？
How doyou think it's going?
什么，你居然没杀他们 是现在不行还是永远不行
What doyou mean, you're not doing it? Not now or not ever?
- 有太多因素了，背景比较复杂 - 背景？
- Too manyvariables. Not enough background. - Background?
好吧，那圣诞节到明尼苏打洲怎样？
Okay, well, how about, uh, born in Minnesota on Christmas Day.
想不想看冰鱼和龙这部电影？
Enjoys, uh, ice fishing and dragon movies.
我要离开这里 我定下来再给你电话
McCabe, I'm out ofhere. I'll call you when I land someplace.
他们会马上派别人来的
They'll just send somebody else, E.
我们所预测的暴风雨终于降临了
The storm we've been waiting- all- finally here.
- 暴风雨移到了西雅图的塔科马地区 - 我到仓库去拿沙袋
- It's moved into the Seattle-Tacoma area. - I'll getsandbags from the shed.
他们在说笑吧，说得这么激动 这只是一场雨而已
You know, this is such a joke. They make it sound all exciting, but you know it's just rain.
你如果不是很忙 就把窗户粘好
Ifyou're not too busy, young lady, feel free to tape the windows.
马上去
Now!
马克
Mark!
我能跟你谈谈吗？
Can I talk to you?
我们能进屋说吗？
Can we talk inside?
当然可以
Yeah, sure.
嗨，到底什么事？
Hey, what's up?
艾比，你能先去里面房间吗？ 我要跟你爸谈事情
Can you go to your bedroom for a minute, Abby? I need to talk to your dad.
快去
Now!
去吧，艾比
Go, Abby.
- 你到底是谁？跟我说实话 - 什么?
- Who are you? Don't lie to me. - What?
他们不仅要杀你
Theywon'tjust killyou.
还要杀了艾比
They'll kill Abby.
- 妈的 - 爸爸
- Damn it! - Dad!
快走
Go!
快跑艾比 到浴室去，快点跑
Run, Abby! Bathroom! Go! Go! Go!
- 别离开艾比 - 好的
- Staywith Abby! - Okay.
艾比
[Mark ] Abby!
- 艾丽卡 - 艾比
- Elektra! - Abby!
谁派你来的？
[ Speaking Japanese ]
你很快就知道了
坏了
Damn it.
退后
Get back!
快点退后
Get back! Go!
走
[ Mark] Go.
他们马上就会到
There'll be more coming.
而且更厉害
What's coming next will be worse.
我想克阮对幻影理事会有话要说
I believe Kirigi wishes to address the Council ofthe Hand.
尊敬的主人
Venerable master...
尽管你是如此的精明能干
despite your delicacy and subtlety...
你却没能处理好能量之源
you have failed to solve the problem ofthe Treasure.
罗侍郎帮主已经把这个任务交给我
Master Roshi gave that task to me.
- 没错 - 我的手下会处理好的
- Yes, exactly. - And my men are taking care of it.
你的手下已经死了
Your men are dead!
是被那个杀手艾丽卡杀的
Killed bythe female, Elektra, the gaijin.
专横的人让人可恨
Your forces are an abomination!
罗侍郎帮主
Master Roshi...
幻影组织绝不能 失去这一代的能量之源
the Hand cannot afford to lose the Treasure for another generation.
所以我诚心的要求接受这个任务
So I humbly request you allow me this task.
也许我还是比较适合的
Perhaps with a little less delicacy...
至少我是不会输给一个女人
my forces will not be defeated by a mere woman.
这个任务就交给你了
The task is yours.
好好完成它 把你的领导能力证明给理事会
Complete it, andyou will have proven yourselfworthy ofleading this council.
我会置身事外
I will step aside.
幻影杀手的人
[ McCabe ] The Hand ofall people.
这次谁帮你摆平这件事情
So who's gonna help you out on this one, E?
- 斯迪克？ - 告诉我他的地址
- Stick? -J ust give me his location.
没问题 我有把握
Sure, no problem. I got it handled.
该死的
Goddamn it.
轮到你了，盲人
[ Sighs ] You're up, blind man.
你双色，我要连进两球然后反弹再进三球 顺序是4 3 2 1 6
Double combo: triple carom on the four-three-two-one-six with a bank massé.
你不用把所有的都想象到这一枪上 这只是第一枪
Uh, you don't need to call all your shots, Pops.Just the first one.
没错就要这第一枪
That is the first one.
哇，你真会跟我开玩笑
Whoa, whoa. Aw, you gotta be kidding me.
8号球在角落里
Eight ball in the corner.
- 盲人？臭屁阿 - 把你的钱放在台桌上
- Blind, myass. - Leave your money on the table.
给你点钱去玩会弹球
Here's a dollar, Abs. Go play some pinball.
- 为什么总是赶我走 - 快去
- Why do I always have to miss the good stuff? -Just go.
艾丽卡，还是那样的走路方式
Elektra. Same walk.
那一种香水
Same perfume.
他们需要你的帮助
They need your help.
到这儿来
Over here.
这是马克・米勒
This is Mark Miller.
马克和他女儿被幻影杀手追杀
Mark and his daughter, Abby, are being chased by the Hand...
他们需要你的保护
andtheyneedyourprotection.
我把他们留在你这里 杀手你来应付，然后我就不管了
I'm leaving them with you. The Hand is your business, not mine.
对了，克阮 他们已经派克阮来了
Ah, Kirigi. They've sent Kirigi.
妈的
Shit.
你有没有问他们 杀手为什么要追杀他们？
Didyou everask whythe Hand was afterthem?
- 他们不知道 - 真的？米勒你不知道?
- They don't know. - Really? Mr. Miller doesn't know?
其实我知道
I do know.
幻影杀手想要的东西 他却不想给
The Hand wantedsomething he couldn't give.
他想逃跑
He tried to run.
然后呢？
And what?
他们杀了我妻子，艾比的妈妈
They killed my wife, Abby's mom.
她不是酒后驾车 是我撒谎了
There was no drunk driver. I lied.
你自己的事情自己解决吧
You're on your own.
你到底为什么要救他们，艾丽卡？
Why didyou reallysave them, Elektra?
难道是为了忏悔？ 为你所作所为赎罪？
Some kind of penance? A down payment on your sins?
她告诉你她实际是干什么的了 米勒先生？
Has she toldyou what she actually does for a living, Mr. Miller?
她救了我和我的女儿 这个已经足够了
She saved my life and my daughter's. That's enough for me.
而你想利用她对你的好感
Thenyou landed on the luckyside ofthe street.
该死你说什么
- Damn, you son of a bitch! - Because with most people-
艾丽卡
Well, Elektra...
你一点没变
you haven't changed.
我们去哪？
What are we gonna do?
艾丽卡？ 我们到底去哪？
Elektra? What are we gonna do?
你快点逃命吧 越远越好，越快越好
You gotta run. As far as you can, as fast as you can.
南美，非洲 改名换姓，改容换貌
SouthAmerica. Africa. Changeyourname. Changeyourappearance.
- 你不跟我们一块走？ - 不
- You're not coming with us? - No.
- 我不能 - 为什么不？你难道没有什么藏身之处？
- I can't. - Why not? Isn't that part ofyour code or something?
我没有，艾比
I don't have a code, Abby.
- 那我们怎么保护自己？ - 我们没有事的，艾比
- How are we supposed to defend ourselves? - We'll be okay, Abby.
我们根本不行
No, we won't.
醒醒吧爸爸，我们力单物薄
Wake up, Dad. We won't!
他们要杀了我们 像对付妈妈那样
They're gonna hunt us down. Just like Mom.
快点进车
[ Breathing Heavily ] Get in the car.
Get in the car!
怎么了？
What's wrong?
她就在下一条街 离停车场三个街区
She's down the street. Three blocks over in the parking lot.
我们要先杀了那个女刺客
We need to kill the gaijin assassin first.
我们现在就动手吗？
Should we go now?
这儿不行 继续跟踪他们
Not here. Keep track ofthem.
我是一个杀手
I'm a soccer mom.
那你真的靠杀人为生？
So, you, um- you really kill people for a living?
对
Yeah.
为什么？
Why?
因为我只会这个
It's what I'm good at.
这种生活好像很难过
That's messed up.
没错
Yeah.
哎，哎 你这鲁莽的杀手
Well, well, the reluctant assassin.
很抱歉托你下水，曼柯
Sorry to drag you into this, McCabe.
我也很抱歉
Me too.
你好，我是艾比
Hi. I'mAbby.
你好艾比，不要站在这里了
Hello, Abby. I'm wondering whatyou're doing here.
我客房很多 赶快到里面去吧，不用客气哦
There's plentyofroom in the house. Go aheadand helpyourselves to whateveryou need.
- 谢谢 - 不客气
- Thankyou. - You're welcome.
你来拌动扳机还是我来？
You want to pull the trigger, or should I do it?
你在给我找罪受
Oh, E. You're crashin' on me, baby.
我是说你已经惹麻烦了 你还在继续惹麻烦
Isaidyou'dcrash, andyou are crashing.
我想找些安全的地方 帮帮我
I just want to get 'em someplace safe, give 'em a chance.
他们已经是活死人了 他们没有机会了
They're already dead, E. They got no chance.
不要跟他们一起送死
Don't go down with them.
我需要护照
I'll need passports.
还有飞机票
- [ Scoffs ] - I'll need plane tickets.
你还要把机票喂鱼吃
Sure. Throw in some season tickets to the Lakers.
进去吧
Go.
你什么都不要告诉她
[Mark] I don't wantyou to tell heranything.
我讨厌撒谎 为什么不能告诉她？
I hate lying. Why can't we tell her?
我们根本不了解她 但她救了我们
- We don't know anything about her. - She saved us.
因为她还不知道我们的真正身份 如果她知道了...
Because she doesn't really know who you are. If she knew-
她是我的朋友 你的朋友？
- She's my friend. - Your friend?
她是我唯一的朋友
She's the only one I have.
我不想死... 你不会死的!
- And I do not want to die with- - You're not gonna die!
不准你再说那样的话
Don'tyou ever say that again- ever.
记住吗？ 恩
- Okay? - Yes.
艾丽卡
[ Girl] Elektra?
怎么了？不好看吗？ 他们帮我改了一下容貌
What's the matter? Is something wrong? They told me to change my appearance, so-
不，你看起来不错
No, it's- You look great.
谢谢
Thanks.
你能教我怎么用这些东西吧 色拉钳子
Can you show me how to use those things, the, uh, salad tongs?
钢戟 钢戟
- Sais. - Sais.
这个不适合你
They're not foryou.
我想学习如何防卫自己
I want to learn how to defend myself.
这是攻击性武器 专门用来杀人
They're offensive weapons. They're for killing.
只能你用
You use them.
我不想你像我一样
I don't want you to be like me.
但我想
I do.
你想学些真的很难的东西吗？
Doyou wanna learn something really, really difficult?
想，是什么？
Yeah. What?
过来
Come on.
坐下
Now sit down.
闭上眼睛 这是什么，瑜伽术？
- Closeyour eyes. - What is this, yoga?
闭上你的眼睛然后呼吸
Just closeyour eyes and breathe.
我在呼吸 我一直在呼吸
I am breathing, I'm always breathing.
还有闭上嘴
And shut up.
安静的坐好
Just sit quietly.
你还好吗？
How areyou doing?
至少我们还活着 谢谢
We're still alive. Thankyou.
不要谢我，马克
Oh, don't thank me, Mark.
你事实上根本不知道我是干吗的
Please, you don't really know what I was doing.
你在那里干什么？
Whatyou were doing there?
我当然知道
Sure I do.
你是去那里杀我们
You were there to kill us.
当你搬到惠尔莱特那儿的时候 我就知道你是来杀我的
I knew it as soon as you took the Wheelwright place.
我不是你适合交往的人
I'm not a good person to get involved with.
我才不管
I'm not asking for anything.
对不起
I'm sorry.
让人讨厌
Yeah, I hated that.
怎么啦？
- [ Bird Squawks ] - What happened?
从昨天开始那只鸟 就一直在这里窥探
That bird's been hanging around here since late yesterday.
他们来了
They're here.
他们来了 我们开车离开
- They're here. - Let's use the truck.
来不及了 这是最快的办法了
- We won't make it. - But that's the best way.
相信我 我们没有时间了
Trust me. There isn't time.
从地窖走 那里有一个密道
Use the cellar. There's a tunnel.
它横穿果园 然后到达正北方的灌木层
Takeyou out past the orchard to the trees. Head north.
那你呢？
What aboutyou?
该死
- [Loads Gun ] - Shit.
走吧
Let's go.
当心点 保证他们的安全
- Be careful. - Keep 'em safe, E.
怪东西
- Holy- - [ Growls ]
不要告诉我你是镇上的马戏团的 我告诉你
Don't tell me, the circus is in town, huh? I'll tell you what.
你最好现在杀了我 我是不会告诉你任何东西的
You might as well kill me now, 'cause I ain't talking.
没有什么好说的
Talking is not necessary.
我答应你前面的请求
- [Yells ] - But I accept the first half ofyour proposal.
他们在树林里
They're in thewoods.
嗨，混蛋
Hey, dickhead.
我跟你赌一千块 你肯定比艾丽卡早死
I'll betyou a thousand bucks you're dead before Elektra is.
等下
Hold up.
跟着我 继续跑
Just follow me. Just keep running.
到那里面去 马克，快点
Get in there. Mark, come on. Go. Go.
艾丽卡
[ Quietly] Elektra.
- Elektra! - Shh.
快跑，艾比
Go! Run, Abby! Run!
快走
Go!
你为什么不告诉我？
Why didn't you tell me?
艾丽卡 艾比不要
- Elektra! - Abby, no!
让我帮她
Let me go!
你就是能量之源是吗？
Ah, you are the little treasure, aren't you?
战争要结束了
The war is over.
战争才刚刚开始
The war has just begun.
退后，艾比
Move back, Abby.
她没事的
She is safe.
后会有期，老人家
Another day, old man.
没事了 你好好休息吧
You'll be fine. Rest now.
不要寻找你的敌人 要感应他在哪里
Don't look foryour opponent. Know where he is.
虽然我瞎了，但我比你看到的更多 因为我不用眼睛寻找
I 'm blind, and I see more than any ofyou, because I don't look.
你没有权利托我下水，斯蒂克
You had no right to drag me into this, Stick.
所有和幻影杀手的战争 都是由她而起，是吗？
This whole warwith the Hand, everything, it's all about her, isn't it?
她是他们的能量之源
They call hertheTreasure.
她四五岁的时候就已经伸手不凡
She was aprodigy from fourorfiveyears old.
很快传到了幻影杀手那里
Wordgot aroundfast.
幻影想让她助他们一臂之力 所以想偷她走
The Hand wanted her for themselves. They tried to steal her.
他爸爸又把她偷回来了 你现在又掺入这件事
- Her father spirited her away. - And you set this up-
原来都是你雇用我 和曼柯去杀他们的
The contract, McCabe, all of this- you hired me to kill them.
是你自己选择的
You're entitled toyour opinion.
一对父女，斯蒂克你居然利用我
A father and his daughter, Stick. You manipulated me.
我有吗？
Did I?
这原来是一个测验
Was all this a test?
从你赶我出去那一天之后的事情 原来都是一个测验
Everything from the day you threw me out, has it all been a test?
如果我失败会怎么样？
What ifl had failed?
有些东西不是教出来的，艾丽卡
Some lessons can't be taught, Elektra.
这个需要自己参透
They must be lived to be understood.
当你来的时候，你的内心充满愤怒
When you came here, you were filled with anger.
你的内心被 暴力和悲愤所侵蚀
All the decencyyou once had, poisoned byviolence and tragedy.
这样是无法达到的
This is not the way.
This is not ourway.
老人家你又在上课
You talk in riddles, old man.
我想让我的学生提高警惕性
It keeps my students alert.
我知道你的心一直是纯真的
I always knew your heart was pure.
你要做的就是要超越自己
You simply needed to see it foryourself.
那艾比呢？
What about Abby?
克阮不死 她就不能离开这里
As long as Kirigi is alive, she's only safe here.
她没有选择
She has no choice.
又偷偷跑到我屋来
Still breaking and entering I see.
对不起
Sorry.
你需要它的 记得要勤加练习
You'll need it. Keep practicing.
对不起我不该对你撒谎
I'm sorry I lied to you.
不用道歉 也没有必要
Don't apologize. You did what you needed to do.
我不想对你撒谎的
I didn't wanna lie toyou.
我爸爸也不想的
Neither did my dad.
我一直很难过没有告诉你
It made me sick not telling you.
每个人都在撒谎，艾比 没有人不说谎的
Everybody lies, Abby. Nobody tells the truth about themselves.
包括你
Including you.
特别是我
Especially me.
解雇人，缩减工人薪水 就是那样
- The layoffs and payroll reductions. - Like that.
恩，还有那个数数
And the, uh, the counting.
- 什么？ - 数步数
- Sorry? - O.C.D.
我没有数步数
I don't have O.C.D.
我小时候数过 但已经是很多年前的事情了
I had it when I was a kid, but I haven't done that in years.
你刚才还在数 当你慢慢走的时候
You were just doing it. When you walk slow like that.
那你在干吗？ 到底是不是在数？
What areyou doing? Areyou counting?
不要无礼
Don't mock me.
不管怎么样我还是你的长辈
I'm still your superior.
也许吧
Maybe.
非要跟我比试一下吗？
Wanna find out?
我要去找我爸爸
I'm gonna go find my dad.
不要乱来
- [ Groans ] - Don't force it.
你再硬来
You're forcing it.
你很快比我更强
You'll be better than I am very soon.
我只是一个小孩 我不想留在这里
I'm just a kid. I don't wanna stay here.
你想怎样？
What do you want?
让我们单独来解决这件事情
To finish it, you and me.
我不需要斯蒂克帮忙，你不能让你爸爸帮忙 赢者拿走一切
No help from Stick, no help from your father. Winner take all.
如果我杀了你 小孩子就是我们的
And when I kill you, the little one is ours.
你不会得逞的 她永远是自由的
And whenyou don't, she is free forever.
同意吗？ 同意
- Agreed? - Agreed.
那在老地方见
We will meet where it all began.
还要老地方结束我们的恩怨
And it will end where it all began.
至少我们做个了断
Foryou, at least.
聪明的孩子
Clever girl.
艾丽卡
[ Girl] Elektra!
怎么了？ 有什么问题吗？
What's the matter? Is something wrong?
我们又见面了
[Kirigi] We meet again.
现在你会记起来
Nowyou'll remember.
放开她
[Abby] Let her go!
勇敢的孩子 你调教的很好
Brave gi rl. You taught her well.
你需要一个新主人
But it's time for a new master.
这就是那个瞎子教的？
Is that what the blind man's been teachingyou?
还不够 你要学会预见敌人
Not good enough. But you'll learn to anticipate your opponent.
艾比 我不会丢下你的
- Abby- - I'm not leaving you.
不过你确实让人担心 就像你一样
- You're a pain in the ass. -Just likeyou.
纹身，能量之源就在这里
Tattoo, the Treasure's here.
跟紧我
Stay right behind me.
跟紧点，艾比
Stay close, Abby.
艾丽卡
Elektra!
魔法耍的不错 我以前领教过
Nice trick. I've seen it before.
艾比，你在哪里？
Abby, where are you?
艾丽卡 可惜不是
- Elektra? - Not exactly.
我曾经是力量之源
You know, I used to be the Treasure...
我不喜欢被人代替
and I don't like being replaced.
我们两个只能活一个
So let's keep your death between you and me.
艾比
Abby!
你不行了艾丽卡
You're slipping, Elektra.
快点，踩水，踩水...
Come on, let's go. Push, push, push.
快点，踩水、踩水...
[Father] Let's go. Let's push, push, push, push!
坚持住，艾丽卡 坚持住
- Keep going, Elektra. Keep going. - [Man ] Don't worry, Elektra.
我只是一个孩子 我会好好照顾她的
- I'm just a kid. - I'll take good care ofher.
我不想待在这里
I don't wanna stay here.
艾丽卡
Elektra.
不要担心，艾丽卡 我会好好照顾她的
Don't worry, Elektra. I'll take good care of her.
艾比
Abby.
该死，快点
Damn it. Come on.
我再也不害怕了
I'm not afraid anymore.
艾比
Abby.
艾比听我说 听我说
Abby, listen to me. Listen to me.
我知道你的心一直是纯洁的
[Stick's Voice ] I always knewyourheart was pure.
但你要超越自己
You simplyneeded to see it foryourself.
嗨，女战士
Hey, warrior girl.
快点醒来
Come here.
醒来，艾比
Come here, Abby.
我需要你 我刚刚找到你
I need you. I just found you.
我刚刚找到你
I just found you.
嗨
Hi.
谢谢
Thankyou.
对不起
Sorry.
你真讨厌
Yeah, I hated that.
下一步准备干什么，克阮已经死了 没有人追杀你了
So, what's next? Kirigi's gone. No one's afteryou.
去上学？
Back to school?
到海滩来个日光浴 还有冰激凌
- Go to the beach and get a tan. - And get ice cream.
噢
[ Laughs ] Oh.
是你重新给我生命
You gave me my life back.
是你让我参悟我的人生
You gave me mine.
我还能再见到你吗？
Will I seeyou again?
我们会在意念内相会
We'll find each other.
希望她不要走我的路
Please don't let her be like me.
为什么不？
Whynot?
其实你还不错
You didn't turn out so bad.
我不想看她太生活的太累
I don't want it to be so hard for her.
这个要由她来决定
That's up to her.
你复活的第二次生命 是不是跟原来的大所不同？
Anyway, your second life's never really likeyour first, is it?
有时候...
Sometimes...
比以前的生活更精彩
it's even better.